Hey there, Astra. I've got a few tasks
today. The first one that I want you to
help me do, I want you to delegate off
to a Codex thread where we take a video
that I made on YouTube a few days ago,
or actually no, it was just yesterday.
So, I want you to turn that into an X
article for me and put it in my X
account.
>> Got it. Let's line that up.
>> So, that X article is ready. Let me open
this up and we'll take a look. We can
see that we have all of this formatted.
We have that 5 by 2 thumbnail that we
wanted that matches our YouTube one. And
now we can see that these screenshots
are coming through. So, the prompt, it
analyzed the entire video, screenshotted
it, put this in here. It even prompted
it if you guys notice. This isn't the
full screen. But it's matching these up
because it understands what am I seeing
in this image and where do I put it in
the text based on the actual article
that was written. Let's also try
something else. So, inside of my school
community, AI Automation Society Plus,
we just did a little bit of a revamp to
the actual course. So, if you could sort
of just like look in there, get
familiarized with that course structure,
and just help me build a really simple,
you know, AIS branded landing page.
>> Yep, I'll start on that.
>> All right, I just got word that the AIS
Plus curriculum page is done and it's
looking pretty impressive. Let's open it
up full screen. Holy, this is actually
the courses. So, I just built this
entire personal OS with just my voice
using GPT-6 Astra voice mode. Now, at a
glance, it might not seem too
impressive, but it had to figure out how
to connect my entire Herc brain. It had
to go pull all the data from these
sources. It had to connect my real
calendar and this is actually
functional. Meaning, here's my actual
calendar and if I came here and I wanted
to add an event right here, we'll just
call this test, save event. This is
actually going to reflect on my real
calendar over here. Now, there are still
a few things that I'm looking to
connect, but I can communicate with my
team through Slack, ClickUp and email
right from this interface. So, I can
open up this conversation and I could
reply to it right here. And I can also
kick off new threads via email or
ClickUp from here as well. And I also
have community polls from YouTube, from
my school communities, what they're
stuck on, and I also have industry polls
from X, YouTube, things like that. The
reason voice mode is so powerful is
because it just uses Codex on the back
end, which means it can look through
your AI operating system and it can do
everything that Codex can do, but you
can control it with your voice and
multitask, kick off different threads.
You can do it from your phone, so you
can literally be on a walk and doing
everything you need to be doing. And the
browser use capabilities from GBD-6
Astra are the best I've ever seen. Right
here on screen, you can just see a silly
example where I gave it two pictures and
I had it paint me in Canva. And this did
take quite a while, but if you think
about all of the little strokes and
everything that needs to do both on the
vision side and the browser use side,
it's actually pretty impressive. Now, on
top of all of the capabilities, you also
need it to have the right context and
connections to actually be useful. So,
when I tell you guys that I've been
talking to Astra in voice mode and it's
just been feeling like it actually knows
everything about me and my business,
it's on another level. So, we just had
an event in July called AIS Live. And
right here, there's over 150 GB of
footage to look through. So, I gave
Codex this link and I basically just
said, "Hey, we need like a 60-second
sizzle reel from this event, like a
recap." And in only two prompts, this is
what I get back, which is really
impressive.
>> Logged off yesterday just buzzing. I had
goosebumps. I was so excited and I had
so much fun.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Cost doesn't justify price. Price
justifies cost.
What is the value of what you [music]
know and what you know how to do?
>> This culture that we have here at AIS is
is just really special.
>> If you think about the actual story that
it told and how much data it looked
through and what it was able to create,
that was really, really impressive, like
I said. So, anyways, let me stop yapping
to you guys and start yapping to GBD6
Astra and show you guys what it can do.
So, all you're going to do is down here
you can see there's a little button
called start new voice chat. You're
going to click on that. And now it's
time to put my headphones in. Hey there,
Astra. I've got a few tasks today. The
first one that I want you to help me do,
I want you to delegate off to a codex
thread where we take a video that I made
on YouTube a few days ago or actually
no, it was just yesterday. It was called
like Astra made this. It made the whole
video. So, I want you to turn that into
an X article for me
um and put it in my X account.
>> Got it. Let's line that up.
>> And while you're working on that, can we
have a separate thread actually start
making the thumbnail for that?
>> Sure. Adding that as well.
>> Now, I do want to make sure that you're
using all my right skills and my right
context. So, make sure you're working
inside of my Herc 2 project for all of
these little tasks that we're going to
kick off today.
>> Got it. I'll make sure that's the
context going forward. The original
article task has been told to stop and
hand off any verified findings. And the
thumbnail task has just been told to
sing.
>> Okay, awesome. Yeah, cuz I see that you
kicked off two regular chats and these
wouldn't have had the same context. So,
it's important that I told you to work
inside my Herc 2 project and now you
should be kicking off the right ones up
there and it looks like you are.
>> Yep, doing that now.
And the article task now has the
thumbnail task's details so they can
coordinate the source, the angle, and
the finished cover. Both replacements
are running inside Herc 2.
>> Awesome. Now, for the actual thumbnail I
want for this X article, I actually
already made one that I really like. Um
the one that I put on my actual YouTube
channel. It was like an image of
um it was like me with my feet up on the
desk and the
OpenAI logo was editing the video. So,
all I really actually need you to do
there is if you could just turn that
into a 5 by 2 version so it fits into
the X article.
>> Sure. I'll update the thumbnail work
with that.
>> Awesome. So,
I know that probably will take a little
bit of time. So, just let me know when
those are done. Let's also try something
else. So, inside of my school community,
AI Automation Society Plus, we just did
a little bit of a revamp to the actual
course. So, if you could sort of just
like
look in there, get familiarized with
that course structure. Um I'm talking
about the AI Automation Society Plus
group.
Inside of that one, if you could just
analyze the structure real quick and
understand sort of like the
transformation from a new joiner to the
end state once they've taken all the
courses, and just help me build a really
simple,
you know, AIS branded landing page that
I could basically send people to if
they're like, "Hey, you know, what is
AIS Plus?" I could send them there, and
they could get a rundown of what that
curriculum looks like. And I want you to
also design that in a way where you use
my ScrollCraft skill to have layers and
to have it be, you know, dynamic and
visual, but don't make it too
overwhelming. So, if you could start
designing that website as well based on
that knowledge.
>> Yep, I'll start on that.
And I'll keep the design dynamic, but
not overwhelming.
>> Awesome. So, now I see that I'm talking
to you in one thread, but then I can
also see when I look at the all the
threads that you're kicking off, I can
see how you're clearly multitasking. And
then by the way, I see the thumbnail
that you made. That looks great. That's
exactly what I was looking for. Will my
other thread that is making the actual
article, it knows that that's there? Oh,
yeah, it looks like you sent that exact
message where I said, "That looks great.
That's exactly what I was looking for."
So, you are able to actually coordinate
these different code assistants to talk
to each other.
>> That's right. The article task has the
approved cover and your go ad.
>> Awesome. Well, while I wait for me to be
able to verify that that all worked,
could you Let's make another improvement
to the Upit OS. Let's see if we could
add I guess let's add another section
for
meetings. I know we already can see all
of my meetings in the actual Herc Brain
visual, but let's add another tab on the
left that just shows
the meeting. So, you pull that in from
Fireflies
and it's just kind of like a nice visual
of the date that the meeting was and
just like
a one-sentence summary of what was
discussed or if there's any important
action items from there. Just so I can
visually see all the meetings that I
had. Um and maybe if there are any
important meetings coming up as well.
>> Okay, I'll take that on.
>> Cool. So, while you're cooking on that,
I'm going to go ahead and actually pause
this voice chat. I'll pick it back up
with you in a bit when you have some
updates for me, but I want to kick off
some voice threads on my mobile device
and see how that all all works as well.
So, I'll be back in a bit. Okay, so
anyways, just wanted to show you guys
what was actually going on here. So, it
made this thumbnail which was actually
based on if I go to my thumbnails, this
one. So, this is the one that I wanted
to use because this is the one that did
best on YouTube and I just needed it to
make that a 5x2. And what you guys will
notice is I didn't tell it to find this
exact thumbnail. It looked through my
YouTube probably to see which one was
the live one. It looked through the
local files to actually build that. Same
thing over here. What happened was I
don't know what it delegated around, but
all I said was I need a an X article for
this. And so, what it did is it had to
pull in the actual video, it's
transcribing it, and now what it's doing
is it's making the X post, but it also
took 11 screenshots. And so, it's going
to place those screenshots in the X
article at the right spot. So, we'll get
to view that in a sec, but I just wanted
to call out what's actually going on on
the back end there cuz it's very
impressive. But now, I need you guys to
look at this. So, you can also do this
on your phone. So, imagine you're on a
walk or you're in your car driving and
you need to kick off some tasks or
delegate some work to your team or
whatever it might be,
because it has all the connections in
here, you're going to go to remote,
you're going to scroll down, and this is
where you'll Oh, wait, right here, this
button. Right here, this is where you'll
start a new voice chat.
And now, it's going to be the same
thing.
Hey. So, I need you to help me kick off
a thread inside of um my Herc 2 project.
What I want you to do is I just need a
nice
rundown of the best use cases that
you've seen, the best viral demos that
you've seen of Astra 6
um you know, GPT Astra 6 on X.
>> Sure.
Sure.
>> So, the point I'm trying to make here is
that I can keep scrolling on my phone
even when it's doing things on the back
and as you can see it's still keeping
this conversation.
>> Got it. I'll keep going here. Yep,
that's exactly it. I kicked off the
Astra research thread and we can keep
talking here meanwhile.
>> Awesome. So, while we're while we're
waiting on all this,
could you just take a look at my you
know, the look at the YouTube space.
Look at some of my past videos and look
at what else is going on in the space
and give me a quick analysis of maybe
some trends and maybe some things to
start preparing for.
>> I'll scan the current landscape now. Big
trends heading toward 2027 are more
AI-assisted production and
personalization, deeper community play
with memberships and owned audiences,
short and long-form blending into one
funnel, and creators rewarded for
building recognizable shows and
perspectives, not just one-off uploads.
>> So, the point I was trying to make there
was just that you can do this on your
phone as well and it's a super clean,
crisp syncing between your desktop and
your phone. So, we've got the Upwork OS
working on adding a Fireflies task or a
Fireflies meeting section, so I can see
that stuff. We've got the X article
being finalized and we'll pull that up.
So, that X article is ready, let me open
this up and we'll take a look. We can
see that we have all of this formatted,
we have that 5 by 2 thumbnail that we
wanted that matches our YouTube one. We
have all of this formatted in a good way
and now we can see that these
screenshots are coming through. So, the
prompt, it analyzed the entire video,
screenshotted it, put this in here. It
even cropped it if you guys notice. This
isn't the full screen. We keep going
down, this is the full screen. This is a
full screen, full screen, but it's
matching these up because it understands
what am I seeing in this image and where
do I put it in the text based on the
actual article that was written. And
there is nothing sensitive in this
video, but what it will actually do too
is if I have like an API key in there or
if I have like a personal email, it
actually will like blur it out. So, it
does that automatically and now that is
just worked into the skill. So, this is
now an article that I would just be able
to read through. All of these
screenshots are taken. They're cropped
if they needed to be. They're blurred
out if they needed to be. And then I can
just go ahead and publish it because it
did all of that with just my voice. We
can also see that this one that I kicked
off from my phone is done. It searched
through X and it found um multiple
posts, one from Ben Davis, one from
Ethan, one from Thomas. You can see that
it gives us the actual link to all of
these threads. So, if I want to click
on, you know, this 3D graphics build, I
get taken straight to that actual post.
1.3 million views. I did see this one.
This one was pretty impressive. We can
see that now we have this little
rundown.
And if we would have stayed on the voice
chat, it would have, you know, told us
about all this. It looks like the Up at
OS one is also done. Let's see what
happened over here. Meetings is live.
So, let me open this up and we'll see.
Actually, I'm going to open this up full
screen. We now have a section called
meetings. You can see on the calendar
I've got one tomorrow. I've got one on
Monday. And we can actually pull up the
actual calendar details. So, if I open
this one up, does this take us straight
to the calendar? Yep, takes us straight
to the actual calendar and we see the
event details there. And now we can also
see past meetings. So, this all-hands,
we can see the team reviewed learning,
community growth, product updates,
operational improvements, AI tools, and
a shared mission centered on customer
happiness. We have an action highlight.
Nate Hurk shared bookmark links to the
most used Google Drive folders. Yep,
yep, yep. And we can see other action
items here. And we can also open up this
recording which takes us straight to
Fireflies. So, that quickly we were able
to develop a new section into our actual
um OS here, which is a combination of
Fireflies and Google Calendar. And I
don't even know if it uses any AI in the
background because Fireflies already
processes these AI action items. Maybe
it hit, you know, the GBT endpoint or
the Anthropic endpoint to actually put
the stuff in here, but really
impressive. All right, I just got word
that the AIS Plus curriculum page is
done and it's looking pretty impressive.
Let's open it up full screen. Build the
skills, shape what's next. And we've got
Holy. This is actually the courses. I
wonder if it
Okay, it takes you down to here. There's
like a curriculum section. Now, I think
this looks really good. It pulled the
picture of me. You also will realize
that the background, right? The
background, you can see these layers.
The mountains are in different spots.
They move in different, you know, paces.
But, what I love that about this that it
did is if I actually go to RA Automation
Society website,
it kept a very similar vibe, right? Like
the blue feeling, the backgrounds
um of the mountains and stuff, even on
the certification tab, it kept the
consistency. Now, honestly, I think
these mountains look a little bit cooler
and there's like fog, but it kept
everything on brand because it was able
to crawl through my workspace, look up
what it needed to look up to make sure
that it actually understood what I was
asking for. And that's what I think is
so cool about Astra is when you give it
a task, it feels like it just will
contextualize and ask you questions and
crawl through things first because it
wants to make it more specific to you.
And that's what is just really, really
cool. I mean, this is This is the actual
curriculum. If I go to IS+ and I go to
classroom, that's exactly what happens.
You know, these are the actual courses
and then over here, uh wrong one.
These are the actual courses that we
have in there. So, it was able to look
through all of that and build out
the actual curriculum. I think this is
really, really slick. So, anyways, guys,
that is going to do it for this one. Get
into Codex and start playing around with
that voice mode. And if you want to
learn more about how I build websites
like this using Astra and using my
Scrollcraft skill, then check out this
video right up here. I walk through the
whole thing. I'll see you guys over
there. But, thanks for watching.
See you guys.